{
    "subject": "resource/Slint",
    "predicate": "property/genre",
    "object": "resource/Post-hardcore",
    "human_readable": "The genre of Slint is Post-hardcore.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6810942888259888,
            "question": "Which music genre encompasses the style of Slint?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6317567825317383,
            "question": "What genre of music is Slint known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5501582026481628,
            "question": "In what genre did Slint achieve recognition?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5250848531723022,
            "question": "Name a musical genre associated with the band Slint."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5194072127342224,
            "question": "Describe the musical style of Slint."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45698004961013794,
            "question": "What musical subgenre is Slint most closely associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3953549861907959,
            "question": "To which music category does Slint belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39528176188468933,
            "question": "How would you categorize Slint's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3932843506336212,
            "question": "What kind of music does Slint play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3588758409023285,
            "question": "What is a defining characteristic of Slint's music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The genre of Slint is Post-hardcore.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7489_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of music does Slint play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7489_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you categorize Slint's music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7489_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which music category does Slint belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7489_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7489_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7489_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7489_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7489_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7489_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7489_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7489_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7489_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7489_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7489_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support this triple. The context information contains several articles that mention Slint, and in each of them, the author refers to the band's music as \"post-hardcore\", among other genres such as math-rock and post-rock. Therefore, the statement \"The genre of Slint is Post-hardcore\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Slint's musical style, describing it as shifting into sounds resembling math-rock and post-hardcore. This supports the statement that Slint's genre is Post-hardcore."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}